export const questions = [
  // {
  //   id: 1,
  //   questionText: 'What does HTML stand for?',
  //   options: [
  //     'HTML stands for Hyperup Marktext Language',
  //     'HTML stands for HyperText Markup Language',
  //     'HTML stands for Hyper Markting Language tool',
  //   ],
  //   correctAnswer: 'HTML stands for HyperText Markup Language',
  //   timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  // },
  // {
  //   id: 2,
  //   questionText: 'What is the basic structure of an HTML document?', 
  //   options: [
  //       'An HTML document typically starts with <!DOCTYPE html>, followed by <html>, <head>, and <body> elements.', 
  //       'An HTML document typically starts with <html>, followed by <html>, <head>, and <body> elements.', 
  //       'An HTML document typically starts with <h1>, followed by <p>, <div>, and <body> elements.', ],
  //   correctAnswer: 'An HTML document typically starts with <!DOCTYPE html>, followed by <html>, <head>, and <body> elements.',
  //   timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  // },
  // {
  //   id: 3,
  //   questionText: 'How do you create a hyperlink in HTML?',
  //   options: [
  //     'You can create a hyperlink using the <a> element, like this: <Link to="https://example.com">Visit Example</Link>.',
  //     'You can create a hyperlink using the <a> element, like this: <href="https://example.com"Visit Example /a>.',
  //     'You can create a hyperlink using the <a> element, like this: <a href="https://example.com">Visit Example</a>.',
  //   ],
  //   correctAnswer: 'You can create a hyperlink using the <a> element, like this: <a href="https://example.com">Visit Example</a>.',
  //   timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  // },
  // {
  //   id: 4,
  //   questionText: 'What does the HTML <br> element do?',
  //   options: [
  //     'The <br> element is used to insert a line cut within text.',
  //     'The <br> element is used to insert a line break within text.',
  //     'The <br> element is used to insert nothing within text.',
  //   ],
  //   correctAnswer: 'The <br> element is used to insert a line break within text.',
  //   timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  // },
  // {
  //   id: 5,
  //   questionText: 'Explain the difference between <ol> and <ul> in HTML.',
  //   options: [
  //     '<ol> is used for ordered (numbered) lists, while <ul> is used for unordered (bulleted) lists.',
  //     '<ol> is used for ordered (letter) lists, while <ul> is used for unordered (slashes) lists.',
  //     '<ol> is used for ordered (Ruman number) lists, while <ul> is used for unordered (ashes) lists.',
  //   ],
  //   correctAnswer: '<ol> is used for ordered (numbered) lists, while <ul> is used for unordered (bulleted) lists.',
  //   timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  // },
  // {
  //   id: 6,
  //   questionText: 'How do you add comments in HTML?',
  //   options: [
  //     'You can add comments in HTML using the <*** This is a comment ***> syntax.',
  //     'You can add comments in HTML using the // This is a comment syntax.',
  //     'You can add comments in HTML using the <!-- This is a comment --> syntax.',
  //   ],
  //   correctAnswer: 'You can add comments in HTML using the <!-- This is a comment --> syntax.',
  //   timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  // },
  // {
  //     id: 7,
  //     questionText: 'What is the purpose of the <div> element in HTML?',
  //     options: [
  //       'The <div> element is a block-low container used for styling other ',
  //       'The <div> element is a inline-level container used for grouping only ',
  //       'The <div> element is a block-level container used for grouping and styling other ',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'The <div> element is a block-level container used for grouping and styling other ',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 8,
  //     questionText: 'How can you add a line of horizontal rule in HTML?',
  //     options: [
  //       'You can add a horizontal rule using the <hr> element.',
  //       'You can add a horizontal rule using the <br> element.',
  //       'You can add a horizontal rule using the <span> element.',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'You can add a horizontal rule using the <hr> element.',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 9,
  //     questionText: 'What does CSS stand for?',
  //     options: [
  //       'CSS stands for Cascading Style Shirts.',
  //       'CSS stands for Cascading Strings Sheets.',
  //       'CSS stands for Cascading Style Sheets.',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'CSS stands for Cascading Style Sheets.',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 120,
  //     questionText: 'What does HTML stand for?',
  //     options: [
  //       'HTML stands for Hyperup Marktext Language',
  //       'HTML stands for HyperText Markup Language',
  //       'HTML stands for Hyper Markting Language tool',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'HTML stands for HyperText Markup Language',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 11,
  //     questionText: 'How do you include an external CSS file in an HTML document?',
  //     options: [
  //       '<script src"style.css"></Script>',
  //       '<link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="styles.css">',
  //       '<script src"style.js"></Script>',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: '<link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="styles.css">',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 12,
  //     questionText: 'What is the purpose of CSS selectors?',
  //     options: [
  //       'CSS selectors are used to select and style HTML.',
  //       'CSS selectors are used to select and style JS elements on a web page.',
  //       'CSS selectors are used to select and style HTML elements on a web page.',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'CSS selectors are used to select and style HTML elements on a web page.',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 13,
  //     questionText: 'How do you center an element horizontally in CSS?',
  //     options: [
  //       'You can center an element horizontally using margin: 0 auto; on the element with a specified width.',
  //       'You can center an element horizontally using padding',
  //       'You can center an element horizontally using border ',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'You can center an element horizontally using margin: 0 auto; on the element with a specified width.',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 14,
  //     questionText: 'How do you create a CSS class that applies styles to elements with a specific class name in HTML?',
  //     options: [
  //       'You can define a CSS class using a period (.) followed by the class name, like this: .my-class {}. Then, you can apply this class to HTML elements using the class attribute, such as <div class="my-class">.',
  //       'You can define a CSS class using a period (#) followed by the class name, like this: #my-class {}. Then, you can apply this class to HTML elements using the class attribute, such as <div id="my-class">.',
  //       'You can define a CSS class using a tag followed by the tag name, like this: div {}. Then, you can apply this class to HTML elements using the class attribute, such as <div>.',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'You can define a CSS class using a period (.) followed by the class name, like this: .my-class {}. Then, you can apply this class to HTML elements using the class attribute, such as <div class="my-class">.',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 15,
  //     questionText: 'What is JavaScript?',
  //     options: [
  //       'JavaScript is a programming language that is used to make web pages interactive. It can be thought of as the language of the web.',
  //       'JavaScript is not a programming language that is used to make web pages interactive. It cannot be thought of as the language of the web.',
  //       'JavaScript is a programming language that cannot interact with web pages.',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'JavaScript is a programming language that is used to make web pages interactive. It can be thought of as the language of the web.',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 16,
  //     questionText: 'How do you write a comment in JavaScript?',
  //     options: [
  //       'You can write a comment in JavaScript using two slashes like this: // This is a comment.',
  //       'You can write a comment in JavaScript using two slashes like this: <// This is a comment //>',
  //       'You can write a comment in JavaScript using two slashes like this: <** This is a comment **>',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'You can write a comment in JavaScript using two slashes like this: // This is a comment.',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 17,
  //     questionText: 'What is a variable in JavaScript?',
  //     options: [
  //       ' A variable in JavaScript is a container that holds data, like numbers or text.',
  //       ' A variable in JavaScript are not container that holds data',
  //       ' A variable in JavaScript is a text that holds data, like numbers or text.',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: ' A variable in JavaScript is a container that holds data, like numbers or text.',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 18,
  //     questionText: 'How do you declare a variable in JavaScript?',
  //     options: [
  //       ' You can declare a variable using the var, let, or const keyword followed by the variable name, like var myVariable',
  //       ' You can declare a variable using the ool, let, or const keyword followed by the variable name, like var myVariable;.',
  //       'Nothing at all',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: ' You can declare a variable using the var, let, or const keyword followed by the variable name, like var myVariable;.',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 19,
  //     questionText: 'What is an alert box in JavaScript?',
  //     options: [
  //       'An alert box is a pop-up window that displays a message to the user. You can create one using alert("Your message here");',
  //       'An alert box is a pop-up window that displays a message to the user. You can create one using prompt("Your message here");',
  //       'An alert box is a pop-up window that displays a message to the user. You can create one using pop("Your message here");',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'An alert box is a pop-up window that displays a message to the user. You can create one using alert("Your message here");',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 20,
  //     questionText: 'How do you write "Hello, World!" in JavaScript?',
  //     options: [
  //       'You can display "Hello, World!" in JavaScript using alert("Hello, World!"); or by writing it to the HTML page',
  //       'You can display "Hello, World!" in JavaScript using innerhtml("Hello, World!"); or by writing it to the HTML page',
  //       'non of the above',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'You can display "Hello, World!" in JavaScript using alert("Hello, World!"); or by writing it to the HTML page',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 21,
  //     questionText: 'How do you write an if statement in JavaScript?',
  //     options: [
  //       'if () {}',
  //       'else () {}',
  //       'nothing () {}',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'if () {}',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 22,
  //     questionText: 'What is a loop in JavaScript?',
  //     options: [
  //       ' A loop is a construct that allows you to repeatedly execute a block of code. Two common types are for and while loops',
  //       'HTML stands for HyperText Markup Language',
  //       'CSS stands for Hyper Markting Language tool',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: ' A loop is a construct that allows you to repeatedly execute a block of code. Two common types are for and while loops',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 23,
  //     questionText: 'What is an array in JavaScript?',
  //     options: [
  //       'An array is a data structure that can hold multiple values in a single variable. Values in an array are indexed starting from 0.',
  //       'An array is nothing.',
  //       'HTML stands for Hyper Markting Language tool',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'An array is a data structure that can hold multiple values in a single variable. Values in an array are indexed starting from 0.',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 24,
  //     questionText: 'How do you add two numbers in JavaScript?',
  //     options: [
  //       'You can add two numbers in JavaScript using the - operator, like let sum = num1 - num2;.',
  //       'You can add two numbers in JavaScript using the * operator, like let sum = num1 * num2;.',
  //       'You can add two numbers in JavaScript using the + operator, like let sum = num1 + num2;',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'You can add two numbers in JavaScript using the + operator, like let sum = num1 + num2;',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 25,
  //     questionText: 'What is React?',
  //     options: [
  //       'React is a JavaScript library used for building user interfaces on websites and web applications.',
  //       'React is a JavaScript library used for building user interfaces on mobile ',
  //       'React is a JavaScript library used for building user interfaces on games',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'React is a JavaScript library used for building user interfaces on websites and web applications.',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 26,
  //     questionText: 'Who created React?',
  //     options: [
  //       'React was created by Facebook.',
  //       'React was created by Amazon',
  //       'React was created by Google',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'React was created by Facebook.',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },

  //   {
  //     id: 27,
  //     questionText: 'What does a <div><div/> do',
  //     options: [
  //       'It contains only <p> tags',
  //       'It contains only HTML tags',
  //       'It contains only CSS tags',
  //     ],
  //     correctAnswer: 'It contains only HTML tags.',
  //     timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
  //   },

    {
      id: 1,
      questionText: '(3a) + 2 = 29, a = ?',
      options: [
        '9',
        '6',
        '8',
        'none of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '9',
      timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 2,
      questionText: '"As fast as a hare" is what kind of creative writing tool?',
      options: [
        'metaphor',
        'similie',
        'alliteration',
        'none of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'similie',
      timer: 25, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 3,
      questionText: 'Which one of these materials are not magnetic?',
      options: [
        'iron',
        'nickel',
        'stainless steel',
        'none of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'stainless steel',
      timer: 25, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 4,
      questionText: 'Tom is thinking of a number, he subtracts it by 5 and then times it by 2. What is the right equation to represent the number Tom is thinking of?',
      options: [
        '(T - 5)*2',
        'T - 5 * 2',
        'T = -5 * 2',
        'none of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '(T - 5)2',
      timer: 95, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 5,
      questionText: 'Which one of these elements are radioactive?',
      options: [
        'Hydrogen',
        'Arsenic',
        'Krypton',
        'none of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'none of the above',
      timer: 95, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 6,
      questionText: 'Click the phrase that shows how Dave danced',
      options: [
        'Dave danced',
        'energetically, twisting and turning',
        'as he flounced through the hall'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'energetically, twisting and turning',
      timer: 55, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 7,
      questionText: 'Jamie is cooking pasta for 7, it weighs 350 grams, how much does each portion weigh?',
      options: [
        ' 60g',
        '70kg',
        '70g',
        'it really depends'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '70g',
      timer: 25, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 8,
      questionText: 'What does DNA stand for?',
      options: [
        'Drinking Nitrogen Apples',
        'Deoxyribonucleic acid',
        'Difussing nutritious artery',
        'none of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Deoxyribonucleic acid',
      timer: 65, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 9,
      questionText: 'What is the cause of earthquakes?',
      options: [
        'Collisions or motion of the seismic plates',
        'Rough winds crack seismic plates',
        'Earth is moved by our feet',
        'none of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Collisions or motion of the seismic plates',
      timer: 55, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 10,
      questionText: 'Which phrase in the following sentence tells us how Amy is feeling: "Amy struggled to get her grip, gasping at the beauty as if making her fall."',
      options: [
        'Amy struggled to get her grip',
        'gasping at the beauty',
        'if making her fall',
        'The sentence does not tells us how Amy is feeling'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'gasping at the beauty',
      timer: 25, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 11,
      questionText: 'Here is a sequence: star, square, triangle, hexagon, circle. what shape will be the 35th shape?',
      options: [
        'square',
        'triangle',
        'circle',
        'hexagon'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'circle',
      timer: 65, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 12,
      questionText: 'How do we know that Ryan won when we see this sentence: "Ryan was it, he ran ahead of Amir, who was in front, and jumped high in the air with accomplishment, turning to see a second place Amir panting."',
      options: [
        'Amir was at front and Ryan ran ahead of him',
        'Ryan jumped high in the air in accomplishment means he must have accomplished something big - 1st place',
        'The sentence says that a second place Amir was panting, How would Ryan turn around to see Amir panting if both of them had finished?',
        'all of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'all of the above',
      timer: 55, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 13,
      questionText: 'At what temperature is Celsius and Faherniet equal?',
      options: [
        '10',
        '-40',
        '300',
        'Celsius and Faherniet are never equal, they start at different temperatures'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '-40',
      timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 14,
      questionText: 'Why does Dora say that Jack is wrong when Jack says that 2:3 is the same as 5:6?',
      options: [
        '2:3 is equals to 2/3 you need to find the equivalent fraction and 5/6 is not it',
        'Dora is wrong in fact, 2:3 is the same as 2 + 3 : 3 + 3 so it is 5:6',
        'None of them are right.',
        'none of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '2:3 is equals to 2/3 you need to find the equivalent fraction and 5/6 is not it',
      timer: 45, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 15,
      questionText: 'Why is it dangerous to go into the inner core?',
      options: [
        'Before you even get there, you have to deal with the rising temperatures in the mantle',
        'Do not forget there is an outer core of liquid nickel which is really hot',
        'Once you get to the inner core, it is of solid nickel - this is hotter than the surface of the sun.',
        'All of the Above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'All of the Above',
      timer: 30, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 16,
      questionText: 'If the length from one A to B is 30km, and the length from B to D is 90km and A, B, C and D equals the same length, how long will it take from A to C?',
      options: [
        '90km',
        '90cm',
        '90 miles'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '90km',
      timer: 25, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 17,
      questionText: '"The dew was wet and the puddles reflected the bright light," what weather is the area?',
      options: [
        'It is raining',
        'It is sunny',
        'It is both',
        'It is neither raining nor sunny'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'It is sunny',
      timer: 50, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 18,
      questionText: '"The cows stood bewildered in the busy town, which was full of cars and people, as they tried to find their way home." Where is the relative clause',
      options: [
        'The cows stood bewildered in the busy town',
        'which was full of cars and people',
        'as they tried to find their way home',
        'There is no relative clause'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'which was full of cars and people',
      timer: 25, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 19,
      questionText: 'Why is climate change a threat?',
      options: [
        'The ice caps are melting',
        'Weather is becoming more unpredictable',
        'Droughts and floods are becoming more frequent',
        'All of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
      timer: 25, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 20,
      questionText: 'How do we already know that x is greater than 10 when we see this statement = (10 - x) > 10?',
      options: [
        'If 10 - x is greater than 10, this means that x on its own is greater than 10',
        'x is not greater than 10',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'If 10 - x is greater than 10, this means that x on its own is greater than 10',
      timer: 30, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 21,
      questionText: 'How many apples are in the orchard if they are 20 oranges in a tree?',
      options: [
        ' 20',
        'none, they only said they are 20 oranges.',
        'they are no oranges nor apples in the field.',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'none, they only said they are 20 oranges',
      timer: 50, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 22,
      questionText: 'Here is the blueprint of the ride to France: 30 people in a coach, 10 seats in the coach is £30, the coach itself is £90, they are 150 children going to France, how much money will the school get, how much will they pay, how many coaches needed, and will they have any money left?',
      options: [
        '£450, £450, they would not have any money left.',
        '£300, £450, they will be in debt.',
        '£450, £300, they will have £150 left',
      ],
      correctAnswer: '£450, £450, they would not have any money left.',
      timer: 180, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 23,
      questionText: '2 people go to the shop, they are 3 types of food, 3 types of drink and 3 types of tables, how many combinations can they choose from?',
      options: [
        '42',
        '27',
        '36',
      ],
      correctAnswer: '36',
      timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 24,
      questionText: 'How does Daisy feel in this sentence and why: "Mother had strictly not to play with them but to play with the other kids, but she felt the urge to - should she disobey her dear mother for such an opportunity to make friends?"',
      options: [
        'Stressed because she can only choose one of the options and one was decided for her and she does not like that.',
        'Happy because she has children to play with.',
        'Angry because her mom would not let her do what she wants.',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Stressed because she can only choose one of the options and one was decided for her and she does not like that.',
      timer: 130, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 25,
      questionText: 'Who was the first person to discover electricity and do we use it today?',
      options: [
        'Nikola Tesla, he discovered AC electricity but we do not use it today, we use DC electricity that was discovered by Thomas Edison',
        'Thomas Edison, he discovered AC electricity but we do not use it today, we use DC electircity that was discovered by Nikola Tesla',
        'Thomas Edison, he discovered DC electricity but we do not use it today, we use AC electircity that was discovered by Thomas Edison',
        'none of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Thomas Edison, he discovered DC electricity but we do not use it today, we use AC electircity that was discovered by Thomas Edison',
      timer: 90, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 26,
      questionText: 'What are the three main types of fossil fuels?',
      options: [
        'coal, gas, rock',
        'coal, iron, steel',
        'coal, gas, oil',
        'coal, fire, gas'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'coal, gas, rock',
      timer: 25, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 27,
      questionText: 'Tom says that 3^5 = 243, what equation below does not?',
      options: [
        '81.5 * 4',
        '243 * 1',
        '3 * 81',
        '9 * 27'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '81.5 * 4',
      timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 28,
      questionText: '"Six Sweet Sizzling Sausages Swam Still Samps" what creative writing tool is that??',
      options: [
        'Personification',
        'Alliteration',
        'Metaphor',
        'none of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Personification',
      correctAnswer: 'Alliteration',
      timer: 50, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 29,
      questionText: 'Which substance does not conduct electricity?',
      options: [
        'Iron',
        'Potato',
        'Copper',
        'none of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'none of the above',
      timer: 25, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 30,
      questionText: 'Why is Asha scared in this extract: "Asha clutched her torch with her sweaty hands and flicked it on, the battery had run out. How inconvenient she thought. Her head began to throb, her stomach was in knots, why could such a predicament happen? She knew something had moved but she just could not spot it, it must have been a human, who was tall and could  match to her eyesight speed. Passing through the pine trees. What if it was a bear? It could be standing up walking faster than my eyes can see. Where was that creature lurking in the shadows? And then she dropped her torch..."',
      options: [
        'She knew something had moved but she could not see it.',
        'She had seen the creature and it looked horrible.',
        'The torch battery had ran out so she could not see.'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'She knew something had moved but she could not see it.',
      timer: 80, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 31,
      questionText: 'Through the text, infer where Asha is and show evidence, the extract is provided: "Asha clutched her torch with her sweaty hands and flicked it on, the battery had run out. How inconvenient she thought. Her head began to throb, her stomach was in knots, why could such a predicament happen? She knew something had moved but she just could not spot it, it must have been a human, who was tall and could  match to her eyesight speed. Passing through the pine trees. What if it was a bear? It could be standing up walking faster than my eyes can see. Where was that creature lurking in the shadows? And then she dropped her torch..."',
      options: [
        ' Desert because she had sweaty hands, maybe because she was hot in the temperatures of the environment.',
        'Forest, she talked about a bear and bears normally lives in forests, Also, it says that they are pine trees, pine trees are also normally in forests.',
        'Rainforest, this is because she was struggling to see who was in the shadows, they are many ways to hide in a place like the rainforest',
        'it really depends'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Forest, she talked about a bear and bears normally lives in forests, Also, it says that they are pine trees, pine trees are also normally in forests.',
      timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 32,
      questionText: 'What is the time of day is it through the text, use evidence to back up you answer the text is provided:"Asha clutched her torch with her sweaty hands and flicked it on, the battery had run out. How inconvenient she thought. Her head began to throb, her stomach was in knots, why could such a predicament happen? She knew something had moved but she just could not spot it, it must have been a human, who was tall and could  match to her eyesight speed. Passing through the pine trees. What if it was a bear? It could be standing up walking faster than my eyes can see. Where was that creature lurking in the shadows? And then she dropped her torch..."',
      options: [
        'Day, because she could identify that they were pine trees.',
        'Noon, she must have had enough vision to see that someone was there - excluding sound.',
        'Night, why would she need a torch to see if someone was there or not? And even then, she became more scared because it did not work.',
        'The text does not tell us what time of day it was'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Night, why would she need a torch to see if someone was there or not? And even then, she became more scared because it did not work.',
      timer: 65, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 33,
      questionText: 'Mother goes shopping for premium eggs from a company, Humble Eggs. The price of eggs 10 years were £2, each year they price grew up *1.5, how much are eggs now?',
      options: [
        '£25',
        '£30',
        '£35',
        'none of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '£30',
      timer: 180, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 34,
      questionText: 'There is another egg-making company, Happy Clucks, that sold eggs for £70 ten years ago, they have went down by 1.5 since then, which brand is cheaper',
      options: [
        'Happy Clucks', // Happy Clucks cost £55
        'Humble Eggs' //Humble Eggs cost £30
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Humble Eggs',
      timer: 180, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 35,
      questionText: 'There is one more egg company, Eggs that go Cheap Cheap, sell eggs for £2, how much what is the range of all the prices?',
      options: [
        '£55',
        '£45',
        '£52',
        '£53'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '£53',
      timer: 65, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 36,
      questionText: 'Tom says that Isaac Newton discovered gravity, what is gravity?',
      options: [
        'a force that gives you metabolism',
        'a force that makes you float',
        'a force which tries to pull two objects toward each other',
        'all of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'a force which tries to pull two objects toward each other',
      timer: 25, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 37,
      questionText: 'Tom also says that gravity and inertia are both the same, explain why he is wrong.',
      options: [
        'Gravity makes us float, inertia keeps us down. ',
        'Gravity pulls objects, inertia resists changes in motion.',
        'Gravity resists changes in motion, inertia pulls objects.',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Gravity pulls objects, inertia resists changes in motion.',
      timer: 60, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 38,
      questionText: 'Explain what hit the main character is in this passage - "I realised that someone was there, he was watching me. But how? Then it hit me, he is not here at all. Something is strange here, but I do not know what. Ever since we went here they have been a series of different things and I cannot bear to have it any longer... "',
      options: [
        'The person hit the main character',
        'What was happening',
        'The air.',
        'Nothing hit the main character'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'What was happening',
      timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 39,
      questionText: 'Max is thinking of a number, he times it by 10, divides it by 2 and then adds 3, he gets 28, what was his starting number?',
      options: [
        '50',
        '25',
        '5',
        '3'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '5',
      timer: 50, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id:40,
      questionText: 'What is the name of the imaginary, horizontal line in the middle of the earth?',
      options: [
        'Prime Meridian',
        'Longitude',
        'Equator'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Equator',
      timer: 25, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 41,
      questionText: 'How much change will you get if you paid £100 for 3 £20 dresses?',
      options: [
        '40',
        '40p',
        '£40',
      ],
      correctAnswer: '£40',
      timer: 25, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 42,
      questionText: '1/2 of 0.25',
      options: [
        '0.12',
        '0.125',
        '0.1255',
      ],
      correctAnswer: '0.125',
      timer: 25, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 43,
      questionText: 'What happens when there are too many components for a cell to handle?',
      options: [
        'It works perfectly.',
        'All the energy is distributed equally, but it is so small that there is not enough power to make them work.',
        'All the energy is distributed to only one of the components so that only one of them can work.',
        'All of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'All the energy is distributed equally, but it is so small that there is not enough power to make them work.',
      timer: 55, // Timer in seconds
    },
    
    {
      id: 44,
      questionText: 'Who created the first battery/cell?',
      options: [
        'Leonardo Da Vinci',
        'Alessandro Volta',
        'Luigi Galvani'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Alessandro Volta',
      timer: 40, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 45,
      questionText: 'What punctuation is used for suspnense?',
      options: [
        ',',
        '.',
        '...',
      ],
      correctAnswer: '...',
      timer: 10, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 46,
      questionText: 'What is the radius of a circle?',
      options: [
        'The length around the circle.',
        'The length around a square',
        'The length of the center of the circle to around it.',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'The length of the center of the circle to around it.',
      timer: 180, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 47,
      questionText: '1 euro = £0.83, how much is a shirt in euros if it is £1.66 ',
      options: [
        '3 euros',
        '2 euros',
        '2.5 euros',
      ],
      correctAnswer: '2 euros',
      timer: 120, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 48,
      questionText: 'How much change will you get if you have 5 euros and buy a £2.85 drink?',
      options: [
        '£2.35',
        '£1.3',
        '£1.29',
      ],
      correctAnswer: '£1.29',
      timer: 200, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 49,
      questionText: 'What does the promise Liam makes suggest about his habits? in the text below: "Liam searched his entire house for the missing key. He checked under the couch, inside drawers, and even in the refrigerator, but it was nowhere to be found. Frustrated, he sat down and tried to remember the last time he had it. Suddenly, he recalled placing it in his jacket pocket the night before. Rushing to the closet, he reached into the pocket—and there it was! Relieved, he smiled, promising himself to be more careful next time."',
      options: [
        'He tends to be able to find things and then remember where they are.',
        'It suggests that he tends to be forgetful or careless with his belongings.',
        'He was desperate to go outside so he promised he would.',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'It suggests that he tends to be forgetful or careless with his belongings',
      timer: 200, // Timer in seconds
    },

    {
      id: 50,
      questionText: 'Why is Liam frustrated in this passage: "Liam searched his entire house for the missing key. He checked under the couch, inside drawers, and even in the refrigerator, but it was nowhere to be found. Frustrated, he sat down and tried to remember the last time he had it. Suddenly, he recalled placing it in his jacket pocket the night before. Rushing to the closet, he reached into the pocket—and there it was! Relieved, he smiled, promising himself to be more careful next time."',
      options: [
        'Because the key was found by his brother.',
        'Because he could finded a good hiding spot for the key and now people will see it.',
        'Because he could not find his key even after searching everywhere',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Because he could not find his key even after searching everywhere',
      timer: 200, // Timer in seconds
    },
  // Add more questions here
];